module.exports.questions = [{
        question: "JSON name/value pair is written as?",
        options: ['name’ : ‘value’',
            'name = ‘value’',
            'name = “value”',
            '“name” : “value”'
        ],
        answer: '“name” : “value”'
    },
    {
        question: "JSON strings have to be in?",
        options: ['single quote', 'double quote', 'single quote or double quote', 'none of the above'],
        answer: 'single quote or double quote'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is not a JSON type?',
        options: ['Object', 'date', 'Array', 'string'],
        answer: 'Array'
    },
    {
        question: "What is the file extension of JSON?",
        options: ['.jn', '.js', '.jsn', '.json'],
        answer: '.json'
    },
    {
        question: "In modern websites what is the common usage for JSON?",
        options: ['To store information remotely', 'To send and receive bits of data.', 'To store information locally.', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 'To send and receive bits of data.'
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is a benefit JSON has over XML?",
        options: ['JSON is more forgiving of poor formatting',
            'JSON has less markup requirements and therefore is lighter than XML',
            'JSON can be written poorly and still be parsed',
            'JSON does not need to be stored in a file to be sent remotely'
        ],
        answer: 'JSON has less markup requirements and therefore is lighter than XML'
    },
    {
        question: 'What does JSON stand for?',
        options: ['JavaScript Object Nomenclature',
            'JavaScript Objective Notation',
            'JavaScript Object Notation',
            'JavaScript Orientated Nomenclature'
        ],
        answer: 'JavaScript Object Notation'
    },
    {
        question: "JSON elements are separated by?",
        options: ['semi-colon', 'line break', 'comma', 'white space'],
        answer: 'comma'
    },
    {
        question: "What keywords are reserved in JSON and cannot be used as keys?",
        options: ['Value', 'Object', 'There are none.', 'Key'],
        answer: 'There are none.'
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these data interchange formats has seen a decline in usage in favor of JSON?",
        options: ['ASCII', 'Plain-text', 'SQL', 'XML'],
        answer: 'XML'
    }
]